{
  "results": [
      {
          "type": "boolean",
          "difficulty": "medium",
          "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
          "question": "The Sniper&#039;s SMG in Team Fortress 2, was originally intended to be the Scout&#039;s primary weapon.",
          "correct_answer": "True",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "False"
          ]
      },
      {
          "type": "boolean",
          "difficulty": "medium",
          "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
          "question": "The Ace Attorney trilogy was suppose to end with &quot;Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney &minus; Trials and Tribulations&quot; as its final game.",
          "correct_answer": "True",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "False"
          ]
      },
      {
          "type": "boolean",
          "difficulty": "medium",
          "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
          "question": "In &quot;Resident Evil&quot;, only Chris has access to the grenade launcher.",
          "correct_answer": "False",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "True"
          ]
      },
      {
          "type": "boolean",
          "difficulty": "medium",
          "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
          "question": "Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater was released in 1999.",
          "correct_answer": "True",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "False"
          ]
      },
      {
          "type": "boolean",
          "difficulty": "medium",
          "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
          "question": "The character that would eventually become Dr. Eggman was considered for the role of Sega&#039;s new flagship mascot before Sonic was.",
          "correct_answer": "True",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "False"
          ]
      },
      {
          "type": "boolean",
          "difficulty": "medium",
          "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
          "question": "Shang Tsung is a playable character in Mortal Kombat XL.",
          "correct_answer": "False",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "True"
          ]
      },
      {
          "type": "boolean",
          "difficulty": "medium",
          "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
          "question": "In the Season One Championship of &quot;League of Legends&quot;, the highest achievable rank was Diamond.",
          "correct_answer": "False",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "True"
          ]
      },
      {
          "type": "boolean",
          "difficulty": "medium",
          "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
          "question": "In Rocket League, you can play Basketball.",
          "correct_answer": "True",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "False"
          ]
      },
      {
          "type": "boolean",
          "difficulty": "medium",
          "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
          "question": "Metal Gear Solid V: The Phantom Pain runs on the Fox Engine.",
          "correct_answer": "True",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "False"
          ]
      },
      {
          "type": "boolean",
          "difficulty": "medium",
          "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
          "question": "In Riot Games &quot;League of Legends&quot; the name of Halloween event is called &quot;The Reckoning&quot;.",
          "correct_answer": "False",
          "incorrect_answers": [
              "True"
          ]
      }
  ]
}